<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on The Lybry</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on The Lybry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 23:14:59 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why the name ?</title>
      <link>/about/name/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/name/</guid>
      <description>Booklordofthedings A unique name isnt it ? But how did it come that way ?
Well the word Book was in there since the beginning. My first online representation was made by me together with my parents and I didnt really just wanted to use my full name, but rather I wanted to use something interesting. And as my main hobby during that time was reading and I wanted something that was cool (english words where cool at the time) so I used Book and my Firstname.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome people</title>
      <link>/about/awesome_people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/awesome_people/</guid>
      <description>Why even make this ? As I have written in the description, these people are awesome and I really want to help and support them. One way to do so is to show of their stuff and link them here so you can check them out if you like.
Impareon They/Them Their pfp and snowfox oc
They are a great artist and also the person I commisioned my current pfp from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All of the Links</title>
      <link>/about/linkdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/linkdrop/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Let the links commence&amp;rdquo; But seriously this is the page where everything is linked
The Lybry: The website you are on right now, a Hub for all of my shenanigans. Like a blog and a gallery.
Twitter: My probably most commonly used social media rn. Tweets about everything.
Youtube: I usually do streams here or more analytical stuff.
Github: The place where I store all of my projects and also this website is hosted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>/gallery/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/gallery/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this is my personal art gallery, everything is ordered in descending order of time made and I will add some text and info to each image. I havent found a better way to do this yet, without having to redo stuff so this should work fine. Also you can use the images on here noncomercially if you link me somewhere visible.
Billie the goat Date: 10th, 02.2021
This is the protagonist of the game billies bust up and I got an earworm from that so I just drew him</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floppy Control</title>
      <link>/projects/floppy_control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 23:14:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/floppy_control/</guid>
      <description>I actually finished a game at some point My original goal since elementary school always was, to become a game programmer, and while currently the focus changed quite a bit to general programming with gamedev as a sidehobby I did learn alot of game programming and in the summer of 2020 I actually finished my first game project for a GameJam.
(A gamejam is a time limited game making &amp;ldquo;competition&amp;rdquo; where the participants make a game based on a certain theme)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>/blogs/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 23:03:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/writing/</guid>
      <description>My main knowledge of the english language comes from the internet and not from school.
This is probably a fairly common for people that have english as their secondary language nowadays, however for me there is the additional problem of actually learning almost nothing during english class.
My teacher was horrible at teaching and basically the entire class agreed to it, so my writing suffered.
After basically being adicted to watching yt and at some point switching to watching it mainly in english, my level of english started to improve, with a big focus there being spoken english.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawabox</title>
      <link>/blogs/drawabox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 18:04:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/drawabox/</guid>
      <description>Today I started the drawabox course. If you are wondering what it is, its
a drawing course that is intended to show people
an organized way to learn how to draw.
https://drawabox.com/
And since I never really learned to draw I decided to start the course for myself, with the goal of doing 2 pages of it a day and hopefully being a better artist at the end of this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Internet</title>
      <link>/blogs/my-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 17:47:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/my-website/</guid>
      <description>This is literally just here as a hello world post If you want actuall content to read maybe look at the project page where I wrote down my thoughts on this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 17:47:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/impressum/</guid>
      <description>This document has a german and an english version, the english version is the second one.
Dieses Dokument hat eine deutsche und eine englisch Version, die englische ist die zweite.
Impressum, DSGVO und Copryright Impressum Verantwortlich für den Inhalt nach § 55 Abs. 2 RStV:
Jannis-Leander von Hagen
Stiftstraße 34
32657 Lemgo
+49 015734951476
Haftungsausschluss: Haftung für Inhalte Die Inhalte unserer Seiten wurden mit größter Sorgfalt erstellt. Für die Richtigkeit, Vollständigkeit und Aktualität der Inhalte können wir jedoch keine Gewähr übernehmen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This website</title>
      <link>/projects/thiswebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 17:47:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/thiswebsite/</guid>
      <description>I finallly &amp;ldquo;finished&amp;rdquo; my website I dont think I will ever truly finish it, as even with this setup right now I am immideatly thinking about making a custom static page generator
The Idea I always really liked the idea of having a website/blog where I can post my own stuff, while not being limited by lenght like on twitter, but also by being more open than a private discord server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/booklordofthedings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/booklordofthedings/</guid>
      <description>So, about me.
Im a 18 year old student living in germany
People usually refer to me as &amp;ldquo;Booklordofthedings&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Book&amp;rdquo; (he/him)
I am very interested in alot of computer science topics and &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; how to program in C#, node js and in Beeflang
There are alot of games and franchises I like, although I dont usually interact with the fandom. Most of them tend to be indie games, although I also like stuff like Plants vs Zombies, Paladins or Pokemon Since I call myself &amp;ldquo;Book&amp;quot;lordofthedings it would be weird if I wouldnt read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still under construction</title>
      <link>/reviews/underconstruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reviews/underconstruction/</guid>
      <description>bruh whyd you even click this ?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
